

Hoang Do

Web developer

About Me

Hello! I am Hoang Do. I am passionate about web development. I am a skilled Back-end Developer, and I am familiar with web frameworks such as PHP-Laravel or Java-Spring. I also have experience with Front-end frameworks like React, Angular, and VueJS.

DOB 02/01/1994

Email hoangdo.2194@gmail.com

Phone +84 35 537 4643

Address Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Professional Skills

PHP - Laravel

Java - Spring

HTML

CSS	
JavaScript	
ReactJS	
Angular	
VueJS	

Work Experience

Web developer at TopCV

January, 2021 - Present

- Maintain and design systems and databases.
- Develop projects and features for the company's production and focus on the TopCV website and the internal operating systems.
- Train for other members, and sometimes take the Project Manager role for small projects with 3-5 members.

Web Developer at Amit Group

September, 2018 - January, 2021

- Designed systems and databases according to customers' requirements, developed and maintained the backend and frontend applications (admin sites) for most projects.
- Performed a full life-cycle of developing and deploying products.

Education

Bachelor in Software Engineering from FPT University

2021 - Present

Get a higher education to obtain the Bachelor's Degree.

Higher diploma in Software Engineering from FPT Aptech

2017 - 2019

Took this course to get the basics of becoming a developer.

Projects

React hook guard the open source

2021

Successfully built a routing and guarding library for Reactjs based on React-Router-dom 5 after three months of working with React and the original react-router-dom library. It helps my colleagues and me control the routing easily with multiple layouts, authentication, and authorization features of React app.

tindohanghieu.com

2019

A web system provides products from high-end brands, where peole can trade or buy popular items.

- Main functions: Social, Chat, Live Stream.
- Responsibilities: Systems design, Backend developer & Frontend developer (admin site), interface intergration, and deployment.
- Language Framework: PHP (Laravel), Mysql, NodeJs (NestJs Framework), Angular.
- Coverage: Backend ~ 70% Frontend ~ 50% (Admin site).

Hoang Cong Car

2018 - 2019

Hoang Cong is a domestic privatized transportation company where customers can easily get a one-way/ round trip by themselves.

- Main functions: Ticket booking, Trip management,...
- Responsibilities: Systems design, Backend developer, Frontend developer (admin site), and deployment.

- Language Framework: PHP (Laravel), MySql, Angular, VueJs.
- Coverage: Backend ~ 90% Frontend ~ 80% (Admin site).

Various Projects at TopCV and Amit Group

2018 - present

Have been developing and maintaining various projects for both TopCV and Amit Group such as the TopCV's website (topcv.vn) and TopCV's internal systems, <u>E-Caf by Pan United</u> using Spring Boot - Java, and <u>tangthuvien.vn</u>,...

Contact

Address

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Phone

+84 35 537 4643

Email

hoangdo.2194@gmail.com



https://www.facebook.com/hoangdo.2194

0

https://www.instagram.com/hoangdo.2194

https://github.com/aaaahoang123